careerboard.com 2013-05-18

# Privacy Policy | the USA CareerBoard.com

 **CareerBoard.com - PRIVACY POLICY**

CareerBoard.com ("CareerBoard") is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to www.careerboard.com (“the Site”). Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. 

**By registering or using this Site, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.**

INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU 

When you visit or register on the Site you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including but not limited to your name, address, email address, and telephone number If you apply for jobs, the information you provide in any application form will also be stored. In addition, if you upload your resume to the Site it will be stored on our server. We may also collect information about your usage of our Site, as well as information about you from e-mails or letters you send to us, or from e-mails you send in response to jobs advertised on our Site.

USE OF YOUR INFORMATION 

Your information will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of our Site and to supply our services, which include providing you with our newsletter, and to contact you where necessary. We will also use and analyze the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business, which may include contacting you to notify you of our current or future services. 

In particular, we may use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the Site or our services. Further, where you have consented, we might also use your information to let you know about other services that we offer which may be of interest to you and we may contact you by regular mail, telephone or fax, as well as by e-mail. 

The information we collect from your usage of our site may be used to contact you by email through our candidate matching technology service where appropriate.

We retain all information and resumes indefinitely. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know or, if you would like us to delete your personal information or to remove a resume that you have uploaded, please either delete your details via your "My Account" login or send an [email](mailto:post@careerboard.com?subject=Request%20to%20Delete%20Account) and provide details of your request. 

CareerBoard reserves the right to retain information that you have requested be deleted where there is a legitimate legal reason why such information or resume should be retained by CareerBoard. 

If you use the "Job Cart" to reply to job listings then your emails will be sent with the relevant personal information to the advertisers via CareerBoard’s servers. 

If you set up our Jobs Alerts Service then you will receive a list of jobs that match your specific criteria, which may include a short advertising message from one of our partners. 

Where you have applied by e-mail for a job advertised on our Site we may contact you periodically by email to keep you informed of the services we provide.

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION 

The information you provide to us will be held on computers solely owned **** by CareerBoard and its group companies. 

Where your consent has been given, your information will be shared with businesses looking to recruit or advertise on this Site. Your information may be accessed by or given to our staff working within and outside the United States and to third party companies whom we may use to provide part of our services. We may also pass aggregate statistical information on the usage of our Site to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you. 

In no circumstances will we pass your information to third parties to enable them to contact you themselves about products and services that they offer. Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent. Finally, if our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.

COOKIES 

CareerBoard uses cookies to store small amounts of information on your computer.   Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your details to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the Site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the Site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalize the content of the Site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features of the Site. If you do not wish to receive cookies in the future, please let us know. 

SECURITY 

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorized persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. No website can ever be completely secure, however, and therefore CAREERBOARD EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES RELATED TO ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF INFORMATION ON THE SITE.

We are dedicated to providing a safe environment for you to conduct your job search.  Although we closely monitor the site against fraud, we ask that you take precautions in the information you are sharing with potential employers. 

Never include your social security number, credit card numbers or bank information on your resume, cover letter or profile information.  Additionally do not provide this information to another party over the phone, email, or through the mail unless you are confident in their identity.   

If you come across a suspicious job posting listed on our site please [notify us](mailto:post@careerboard.com?subject=Suspicious%20Job%20Posting).

ACCESSING AND UPDATING 

You are entitled to see the information supplied by you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. 

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY 

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the Site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification. 

CONTACT 

Please [email](mailto:post@careerboard.com?subject=Question%20Related%20to%20Use%20of%20Information) comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed.
